[
    {
        "answer": "EXTORTION",
        "question": "518 PC",
        "id": "question1"
    },
    {
        "answer": "DEFRAUDING AN INNKEEPER",
        "question": "537 PC",
        "id": "question2"
    },
    {
        "question": "537 e PC",
        "answer": "manufacturer's serial number removed / altered",
        "id": "question3"
    },
    {
        "question": "538 d PC",
        "answer": "impersonating a police officer",
        "id": "question4"
    },
    {
        "question": "594 (a) PC",
        "answer": "malicious mischief (vandalism)",
        "id": "question5"
    },
    {
        "answer": "failure to stop at a red light",
        "question": "21453 (a) CVC",
        "id": "question6"
    },
    {
        "question": "647 (a) PC",
        "answer": "soliciting for lewd conduct",
        "id": "question7"
    },
    {
        "question": "647 (b) PC",
        "answer": "soliciting for prostitution",
        "id": "question8"
    },
    {
        "answer": "drunk in public",
        "question": "647 (f) PC",
        "id": "question9"
    },
    {
        "question": "647 (j) PC",
        "answer": "disorderly conduct: prowling / peeping",
        "id": "question10"
    },
    {
        "answer": "obscene or harassing phone calls",
        "question": "653 m PC",
        "id": "question11"
    },
    {
        "question": "21510 PC",
        "answer": "switchblade knife, blade two inches or more",
        "id": "question12"
    },
    {
        "answer": "trespassing",
        "question": "602 PC",
        "id": "question13"
    },
    {
        "question": "26350 PC",
        "answer": "person wearing unloaded handgun in / out of vehicle",
        "id": "question14"
    },
    {
        "answer": "parole violation",
        "question": "3056 PC",
        "id": "question15"
    },
    {
        "answer": "escape",
        "question": "4532 PC",
        "id": "question16"
    },
    {
        "question": "601 W & I",
        "answer": "uncontrollable juvenile",
        "id": "question17"
    },
    {
        "answer": "juvenile violating a court order",
        "question": "602 W & I",
        "id": "question17.5"
    },
    {
        "answer": "false info to officer",
        "question": "31 CVC",
        "id": "question18"
    },
    {
        "question": "2800.1 (a) CVC",
        "answer": "evading pursuing peace officer",
        "id": "question19"
    },
    {
        "answer": "expired registration",
        "question": "4000 (a) CVC",
        "id": "question20"
    },
    {
        "answer": "no front license plate",
        "question": "5200 (a) CVC",
        "id": "question21"
    },
    {
        "answer": "authority to arrest, failure to sign citation",
        "question": "40302 (b) CVC",
        "id": "question22"
    },
    {
        "question": "10851 (a) CVC",
        "answer": "stolen vehicle",
        "id": "question23"
    },
    {
        "question": "10851 R",
        "answer": "recovered stolen vehicle",
        "id": "question24"
    },
    {
        "question": "10852 CVC",
        "answer": "tampering with stolen vehicle",
        "id": "question24.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "10750 CVC",
        "answer": "tampering with vehicle identification number (VIN)",
        "id": "question25"
    },
    {
        "question": "12500 (a) CVC",
        "answer": "unlicensed driver",
        "id": "question26"
    }
]